Would you give up what you need... to get everything you want?
Grace Unplugged is a drama, music film directed by Brad J. Silverman.
A talented young singer and aspiring songwriter’s Christian faith and family ties are tested when she defies her worship-pastor father and
pursues pop-music stardom in GRACE UNPLUGGED, a moving and inspiring new film that explores the true meaning of success.
Gracie Trey, played by AJ Michalka.
Johnny Trey, played by James Denton.
Frank "Mossy" Mostin, played by Kevin Pollak.
Michelle Trey, played by Shawnee Smith.
Quentin, played by Michael Welch.
Rachel, played by Jamie Grace.
Grace Unplugged is a 2013 Christian drama film.
The film is based on the parable of The Prodigal Son and a story
by Brandon Rice, written and directed by Brad J.
Silverman, and stars AJ Michalka, Jamie Grace, Shawnee
Smith, James Denton, and Kevin Pollak.
The film follows an 18-year-old woman who rejects her father's desire for her
to be a church singer and goes to Hollywood seeking stardom.
The film was released to theaters in the United States on October
4, 2013, by Lionsgate and Roadside Attractions.
It was co-produced by Orion Pictures in their first film during its
relaunch by MGM under the banner since One Man's Hero in 1999.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.